epicski.com 2002-12-04

# EpicSki Privacey Statement

**EpicSki Privacy Statement**

EpicSki has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We'll cut to the chase: EpicSki does not share personal e-mail addresses or IP numbers with third parties at all (barring legal action) \- period! For more details, read on…

**Information Automatically Logged**  
Like all websites, your IP number (internet connection id) is automatically logged when you visit EpicSki. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to evaluate site traffic levels (this evaluation does not identify you personally, just the aggregate number of unique users). IP address logging also enables the banning of individual users from the website when a member consistently and severely violate the terms and conditions to which each member agreed when he/she registered. 

**Cookies**  
The EpicSki forums uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the site and to "remember" which posts are new since your last visit (these are identified by yellow light bulbs and yellow folders), in order to enhance your experience at EpicSki.

**E-Mail Address Collection & Use**  
The EpicSki forum's registration form requires members to provide their e-mail address. This e-maill address is used for administrative communication exclusively between EpicSki and and that member -- many of these correspondences are automated features (notification of a reply to your post or notification of a new private message) that you may disable in the "My Profile" control panel. E-mail address collection also enables the banning of individual users from the website when a member consistently and severely violate the terms and conditions to which each member agreed when he/she registered.

**Other Info Collection & Use**  
Other requiredinformation (e.g., username), and additional optional information (e.g., location, etc...), is collected in the registration form and is available for all users to access from a link above each post you make. The purpose of this information is so that readers of the forum will get a better understanding of the people with whom they are communicating in the forum. This does not apply to personal contact information or any information that you do not voluntarily provide yourself.

**External Links**  
This website contains links to other websites, many of which posted by members and not by the EpicSKi administrators. EpicSki is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. None of the information you provide on the registration form is transferred to them.

EpicSki does not participate AT ALL with any of the marketing networks (such as DoubleClick) that pool, share and monitor activity across multiple sites. EpicSki's information is collected and used solely for user experience enhancing features and admin within the EpicSki site boundaries.

**Special Relationships**   
EpicSki is not affiliated with any ski manufacturers, ski resorts, professional associations, or other organizations. EpicSki is an independent operation.

**Public Forums**  
EpicSki makes forums/message-boards/news-groups available to a large community of independent users. Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to share any of your personal information. We suggest using our private messaging feature should you desire to contact others (this allows contact without disclosing personal information). 

When you post personal contact or identification material in one of EpicSki's public arenas (and ALL of EpicSki's forums are public), you are choosing to make that information public and EpicSki bears no responsibility for any undesired outcomes or uses of that information by others, including other registered members of EpicSki. 

EpicSki has no control over the behavior of registered members of its forums, other than banning them from further posting if they prove to be destructive to the community. None of the members of this community are employees or in any way associated with EpicSki; everyone in these forums found the website on their own in and registered on their own in order to interact with other unaffiliated (unaffiliated with EpicSki) individuals. Hence the term "public" forum.

**Free E-Mail Service (Completely Separate from the Forums)**  
A completely separate function from the forum is the free e-mail service where you get your own "you@EpicSki.com" e-mail address. This service requires separate registration from the forum and is independent from the rest of the EpicSki website. This service and all activity pertaining to those e-mail addesses is controlled and administered by Everyone.net -- a third party to whom EpicSki refers users who desire this feature. Everyone.net and that entire free e-mail (you@epicski.com) feature has its own privacy policy which can be found here: [Private E-Mail Service Privacy Policy](http://www.everyone.net/main/html/p_policy.html). Other than lending its "@epicski.com" name and linking to Everyone.net's website (where the service is administered), EpicSki has no role and no control over what is done there. EpicSki has, however, found them to be reliable and responsible in the past.

Feel free to send questions or inquire about any additional issues of concern not addressed in this policy statement: [info@EpicSki.com](mailto:info@EpicSki.com)
